{
	"response_code": 0,
	"results": [
      {
        "category": "McDonald's",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What are the elements of food-safety pre-shift checklist?",
        "correct_answer": "People, Products, Equipment, Procedures",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "People, Productivity, Equipment, Products",
          "Person, Products, Equipment, Procedural environment",
          "People, Products, Equality, Procedures"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "McDonald's",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What is the temperature of hashbrown?",
        "correct_answer": "175 째C",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "182 째C",
          "168 째C",
          "174 째C"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "McDonald's",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What are the inner packages of breakfast ham?",
        "correct_answer": "18 X 240g",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "20 X 240g",
          "18 X 250g",
          "15 X 200g"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "McDonald's",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What is the minimum shelf life on delivery for breakfast ham?",
        "correct_answer": "28 days",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "30 days",
          "25 days",
          "42 days"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "McDonald's",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What is the secondary shelf life of breakfast ham?",
        "correct_answer": "48 hours in chiller including 6 hours defrost.",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "48 hours in chiller including 4 hours defrost.",
          "24 hours in chiller including 2 hours defrost.",
          "36 hours in chiller including 6 hours defrost."
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "McDonald's",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What is the unit/case attribute of porridge?",
        "correct_answer": "100 X 30g",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "100 X 50g",
          "30 X 100g",
          "90 X 30g"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "McDonald's",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What is the minimum shelf life on delivery for porridge?",
        "correct_answer": "150 days",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "130 days",
          "200 days",
          "50 days"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "McDonald's",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What are the inner packages of bacon roll?",
        "correct_answer": "8 X 6",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "8 X 7",
          "10 X 6",
          "6 X 5"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "McDonald's",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What is the minimum shelf life on delivery for bacon roll?",
        "correct_answer": "90 days",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "50 days",
          "70 days",
          "30 days"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "McDonald's",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What is the tempering of bacon roll?",
        "correct_answer": "48 hours included 2 hours defrost.",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "48 hours included 1 hour defrost.",
          "24 hours included 2 hours defrost.",
          "48 hours included 4 hours defrost."
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "McDonald's",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What are the inner packages of brown sauce?",
        "correct_answer": "18 X 300g",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "16 X 300g",
          "18 X 250g",
          "100 X 30g"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "McDonald's",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What is the minimum shelf life for brown sauce?",
        "correct_answer": "50 days",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "90 days",
          "42 days",
          "25 days"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "McDonald's",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What are the inner packages of ketchup?",
        "correct_answer": "2 X 10lts",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "2 X 15lts",
          "3 X 10lts",
          "20lt"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "McDonald's",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What is the minimum shelf life on delivery for ketchup?",
        "correct_answer": "30",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "50",
          "42",
          "93"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "McDonald's",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What is the cooking temperature of poached eggs?",
        "correct_answer": "129",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "182",
          "168",
          "175"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "McDonald's",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What is the cooking time for poached eggs?",
        "correct_answer": "150 sec",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "155 sec",
          "270 sec",
          "180 sec"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "McDonald's",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What are the inner packages of hashbrown?",
        "correct_answer": "8 X 25",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "8 X 50",
          "7 X 20",
          "10 X 30"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "McDonald's",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What is the minimum shelf life on delivery for hashbrown?",
        "correct_answer": "60 days",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "90 days",
          "120 days",
          "50 days"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "McDonald's",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What is the tempering for english muffins?",
        "correct_answer": "48 hours including 2 hours defrost.",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "48 hours including 4 hours defrost.",
          "24 hours including 2 hours defrost.",
          "24 hours including 1 hour defrost."
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "McDonald's",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What is the tempering of toasties flatbread?",
        "correct_answer": "48 hours including 4 hours defrost.",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "48 hours including 6 hours defrost.",
          "36 hours including 4 hours defrost.",
          "24 hours including 2 hours defrost."
        ]
      },
    {
      "category": "McDonald's",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is the tempering of pancakes?",
      "correct_answer": "96 hours in chiller including 12 hours defrost.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "86 hours in chillers including 12 hours defrost.",
        "72 hours in chillers including 6 hours defrost.",
        "96 hours in chillers including 8 hours defrost."
      ]
    }
	]
}
